New York State Defenders Association (NYSDA); Records apap110
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Death Penalty, News Clippings, 1996 December 13-31 (Box 9 (New York State Defenders Association Records), Folder 18)
- Death Penalty, News Clippings, 1997 January 1-18 (Box 9 (New York State Defenders Association Records), Folder 19)
- Death Penalty, News Clippings, 1997 January 18-31 (Box 9 (New York State Defenders Association Records), Folder 20)
- Death Penalty, News Clippings, 1997 February (Box 10 (New York State Defenders Association Records), Folder 1)
- Death Penalty, News Clippings, 1997 March 1-19 (Box 10 (New York State Defenders Association Records), Folder 2)
- Death Penalty, News Clippings, 1997 March 19-31 (Box 10 (New York State Defenders Association Records), Folder 3)
- Death Penalty, News Clippings, 1997 April 1-13 (Box 10 (New York State Defenders Association Records), Folder 4)
- Death Penalty, News Clippings, 1997 April 13-27 (Box 10 (New York State Defenders Association Records), Folder 5)
- Death Penalty, News Clippings, 1997 April 27-May 12 (Box 10 (New York State Defenders Association Records), Folder 6)
- Death Penalty, News Clippings, 1997 May 12-29 (Box 10 (New York State Defenders Association Records), Folder 7)
- Death Penalty, News Clippings, 1997 May 29-June 4 (Box 10 (New York State Defenders Association Records), Folder 8)
- Death Penalty, News Clippings, 1997 June 4-10 (Box 10 (New York State Defenders Association Records), Folder 9)
- Death Penalty, News Clippings, 1997 June 10-14 (Box 10 (New York State Defenders Association Records), Folder 10)
- Death Penalty, News Clippings, 1997 June 14-16 (Box 10 (New York State Defenders Association Records), Folder 11)
- Death Penalty, News Clippings, 1997 June 16-21 (Box 10 (New York State Defenders Association Records), Folder 12)
- Death Penalty, News Clippings, 1997 June 21-30 (Box 10 (New York State Defenders Association Records), Folder 13)
- Death Penalty, News Clippings, 1997 July 1-24, 1997 (Box 10 (New York State Defenders Association Records), Folder 14)
- Death Penalty, News Clippings, 1997 July 24-August 9 (Box 10 (New York State Defenders Association Records), Folder 15)
- Death Penalty, News Clippings, 1997 August 9-21 (Box 10 (New York State Defenders Association Records), Folder 16)
- Death Penalty, News Clippings, 1997 August 21-September 11 (Box 10 (New York State Defenders Association Records), Folder 17)
- Death Penalty, News Clippings, 1997 October 1-10 (Box 11 (New York State Defenders Association Records), Folder 1)
- Death Penalty, News Clippings, 1997 October 10-31 (Box 11 (New York State Defenders Association Records), Folder 2)
- Death Penalty, News Clippings, 1997 November 1-12 (Box 11 (New York State Defenders Association Records), Folder 3)
- Death Penalty, News Clippings, 1997 November 12-30 (Box 11 (New York State Defenders Association Records), Folder 4)
- Death Penalty, News Clippings, 1997 December 1-13 (Box 11 (New York State Defenders Association Records), Folder 5)
- Death Penalty, News Clippings, 1997 December 13-24 (Box 11 (New York State Defenders Association Records), Folder 6)
- Death Penalty, News Clippings, 1997 December 24-31 (Box 11 (New York State Defenders Association Records), Folder 7)
- Death Penalty, News Clippings, 1998 January 1-7 (Box 11 (New York State Defenders Association Records), Folder 8)
- Death Penalty, News Clippings, 1998 January 7-9 (Box 11 (New York State Defenders Association Records), Folder 9)
- Death Penalty, News Clippings, 1998 January 9-19 (Box 11 (New York State Defenders Association Records), Folder 10)
- Death Penalty, News Clippings, 1998 January 19-31 (Box 11 (New York State Defenders Association Records), Folder 11)
- Death Penalty, News Clippings, 1998 February 1-6 (Box 11 (New York State Defenders Association Records), Folder 12)
- Death Penalty, News Clippings, 1998 February 6-16 (Box 11 (New York State Defenders Association Records), Folder 13)
- Death Penalty, News Clippings, 1998 February 16-28 (Box 11 (New York State Defenders Association Records), Folder 14)
- Death Penalty, News Clippings, 1998 March 1-17 (Box 11 (New York State Defenders Association Records), Folder 15)
- Death Penalty, News Clippings, 1998 March 17-30 (Box 11 (New York State Defenders Association Records), Folder 16)
- Death Penalty, News Clippings, 1998 March 30-April 9 (Box 11 (New York State Defenders Association Records), Folder 17)
- Death Penalty, News Clippings, 1998 April 9-23 (Box 11 (New York State Defenders Association Records), Folder 18)
- Death Penalty, News Clippings, 1998 April 23-30 (Box 11 (New York State Defenders Association Records), Folder 19)
- Death Penalty, News Clippings, 1998 May 1-16 (Box 12 (New York State Defenders Association Records), Folder 1)
- Death Penalty, News Clippings, 1998 May 16-31 (Box 12 (New York State Defenders Association Records), Folder 2)
- Death Penalty, News Clippings, 1998 June 1-6 (Box 12 (New York State Defenders Association Records), Folder 3)
- Death Penalty, News Clippings, 1998 June 6-10 (Box 12 (New York State Defenders Association Records), Folder 4)
- Death Penalty, News Clippings, 1998 June 10-15 (Box 12 (New York State Defenders Association Records), Folder 5)
- Death Penalty, News Clippings, 1998 June 15-30 (Box 12 (New York State Defenders Association Records), Folder 6)
- Death Penalty, News Clippings, 1998 July 1-10 (Box 12 (New York State Defenders Association Records), Folder 7)
- Death Penalty, News Clippings, 1998 July 10-23 (Box 12 (New York State Defenders Association Records), Folder 8)
- Death Penalty, News Clippings, 1998 July 23-31 (Box 12 (New York State Defenders Association Records), Folder 9)
- Death Penalty, News Clippings, 1998 August 1-12 (Box 12 (New York State Defenders Association Records), Folder 10)
- Death Penalty, News Clippings, 1998 August 12-21 (Box 12 (New York State Defenders Association Records), Folder 11)
- Death Penalty, News Clippings, 1998 August 21-31 (Box 12 (New York State Defenders Association Records), Folder 12)
- Death Penalty, News Clippings, 1998 September 1-13 (Box 12 (New York State Defenders Association Records), Folder 13)
- Death Penalty, News Clippings, 1998 September 13-30 (Box 12 (New York State Defenders Association Records), Folder 14)
- Death Penalty, News Clippings, 1998 October 1-15 (Box 12 (New York State Defenders Association Records), Folder 15)
- Death Penalty, News Clippings, 1998 October 15-31 (Box 12 (New York State Defenders Association Records), Folder 16)